yeah what up guys all right I'll wait
for few people to get in here no secrets
what up what up what up just make sure
this went out on Twitter good I got a
message on Twitter well let's see what
my request is sometime we should do
public shaming of the people who uh oh
okay alright alright nevermind that was
that was a good yeah thanks yeah go good
um yeah sometime we should do public
shaming or the people who email me and
send me like these like like just just
horrendously bad pitches um so I'll show
you guys
here's our prototype gray panda check it
out this is a little I gotta fix up the
u-blox firmware sorry I gotta fix up the
nothing looks fun where the the serial
firmware in the Panda to make it live
stream everything better
but know what we're here to talk about
today is to let you in the body like you
to check out okay
humans are coming Gilson real soon guys
real soon you know always soon oh um
good but no actually here to talk about
the Corolla we rented a Toyota Corolla
and here it's beautiful
57 scope yeah all right all right what
do we got down here is this that's not
the Corolla where to go Prius um there's
our rav4 Ricardo is that Corolla is this
it here
yes there is this still life
you come back oh it's lagging no no okay
Wi-Fi I'm sorry guys
I didn't make I didn't make the cell
phone pin I didn't make the cell phone
network you want to pull that when you
pull that piece out cool okay
oh you know the same as the usual Toyota
stuff you just remove that thing from
the rear view mirror now it's good right
we go bro good boy you good bro no
gaming quality so what's really nice
about the Toyotas is they all have the
same interface which is not true about
the Honda's where there's at least well
how many different plugs have we said I
guess there's really only seen three
plugs yeah that relax well and then
there's the Odyssey which has the same
plug but upside down so we're just gonna
plug in our toyota giraffe here
available shop comedy I always be
plugging March should work and so there
we go we're in a Toyota giraffe we have
a panda we're gonna plug it into this
ego on over here oh yeah
all right and then we should let the car
home to grab you go for mounting another
Spina because I need to fingerprint a
cow first got it guys this is the same
thing that we do know we're not doing a
fusion port we are only we're really
focusing on Toyota this year so oh
you're not powering it yes so you have
to power it otherwise appear no I wanna
choose the started swish-swish thing
yeah there we go
is it connected yeah all right good good
here we go okay cool cool camera next
yeah all right I do want a sensation
from the arrow do you want to go get out
nice eh phone from here okay we could go
get one of the new uh oh the new life
though new laptops yeah yeah we have new
laptops designed for making development
easier could someone explain other
Toyota's are superior to the fourth well
first off there's a whole lot more
Toyotas than Ford's you wanna maybe pull
forward a little so we can get better on
the Wi-Fi make the quality higher you
guys so we're getting we're getting
Wi-Fi from the house um
Toyota's aren't Ford's no that is that
is good that is definitely true on the
driveway ah oh
is anyone in out of the back well no I
guess do you want to take it out though
right
well I just gotta take a while it's
gonna take a while cool loving the
rear-view mirror set up ya know we keep
the rear view mirrors on cars now we
don't take them out we used to take them
out but then through illegal things
Toyota is far more reliable than Ford
yeah that's probably true what's Cody no
there's no light our guys there's no
light all right there will be HD Maps
what up how do you add to the fusion
boundary um I would actually love to see
someone pour it one of the Fords it
shouldn't be that hard it's lagging
again
I thought we fixed the lag no no no no
no no oh wait we're on LTE for some
reason I don't know why Wi-Fi is not
working
all right should be very good now it's
not better Cody's a movie player oh I
don't know about movies on the odds bus
but yeah so is that open source script
get fingerprint yes open source it 0.40
my truth yeah so we have a script now to
get fingerprint so it's getting the
fingerprint here from the car so the
best thing is if you run it by having a
car cycle so there are some messages
that I like slow ok so you can see and
so to get them it's better like if you
start up the car some of them are sent
right the way when you start the car
those steel Athey cool hey did you watch
me before yeah let's let's wait few more
seconds I forget exactly have a
fingerprint of work so it's like having
more messages is okay you want to have
all the messages because if you get a
message that is not in your fingerprint
he's gonna think that it's not it's not
okay okay got it
it goes by exclusion you want to get
them all yes
so we now have a fingerprint yeah
which this is all this is all documented
on our wiki yeah it is dropping really
so a course
we have we have some some predator
Helios 300s the Dell is actually nice we
can go look at our liner later we do
have some lighters get t-mobile we have
t-mobile and all the other of the other
things oh you want to go landscape
alright alright guys so we have some
exciting news
we found a box full of pandas so these
are gonna ship out
hella soon browse we got all these
pandas ready to go so you know it's it's
one to six weeks if you're on the
earlier end of the one to six weeks
you're gonna be getting a panda very
shortly
check out these heat sinks from eons all
right you guys here's the here's the
Aeon build plan you know we got to get
we got to get all the neons built but um
yeah let's make sure the god of secrets
you guys you've seen the Calvi sign
what does the finger prick different
standard versus a high weights by an
external Wi-Fi repeater we're actually
gonna do that well we're kinda getting a
better Wi-Fi in the backyard cool guys
well we'll check in on this later we're
gonna try to do the toyota corolla port
in one day one day toyota corolla port
we will certainly work on getting better
Wi-Fi outside i understand how the
streams are hard to watch when it's
laggy any new Nvidia stuff want to see
your Nvidia stuff will show you Aaron
video stuff
it's pretty nice in video they really
come aways and improving the like
quality of the experience of the
hardware you can get for them if you are
a self-driving car company we recommend
working with in video they don't super
easy to work with you today like hooked
us up with all this stuff it's kind of
hard to ship which is why we're not
working on it just yet a lot of the
stuff we're doing is still it's still
mobile phones which all have
unfortunately Qualcomm maybe maybe the
next Aeon we'll have a Nintendo
switchman Nintendo switch has a
hesitates to two or one which labels
self-driving car company is the mooing
doing the most damage oh no I don't
think any of them we're really doing
damage I mean some people just like like
you look at I really don't like what uh
I'll sit on to the quality sign we'll do
a little Q&A for the periscope um I
really don't like what like like Ford
does when they talk about all smart
cities cities of the future like this
kind of hype it's it's it's it's bad
because it's it's setting people's
expectations to be unrealistic um it's
not really bad to be honest like none of
this stuff really matters I'm a big
believer in like what you say doesn't
matter that much you know you can you
can say whatever you want your PR and
who cares right if you're measuring
based on PR metrics it might matter if
you're measuring based on like profit
and revenue it doesn't matter
look at Comcast look at all the money
Comcast Maggi everyone hates them right
Comcast could literally say we hate you
and you know people still buy the
Internet
it's a fact Tesla has an interesting
brand but Brenda kind of stupid you the
truth is Tesla just ships the best the
best electric car you can buy by far
cool thanks for joining we'll check back
on this later and there will be updates
throughout the day of our Toyota Corolla
port and this is just because team
localizer is taking a long time um team
localizer team localizer is a very hard
task ahead of them so let's not be too
hard on team localizer but we're gonna
be able to localize with
hence enemy precision in our HD Maps
we're really close to it we have it
working offline we just need to get this
thing working
online and then you guys know that by
the end of the year we are going to open
source all of our HD maps I think
they're gonna be nicer than a lot of the
ones that are out there today I'm
completely automatically generated using
machine learning so we are looking at
putting you know companies like here
Maps companies like deep map TomTom all
of these companies their entire product
we're gonna give away a better version
of it completely free yeah there's a bit
of refactoring going on - so the Toyota
Corolla should get easier but just
remember guys if you're out there
working at an HD mapping company it's
not our core product we make money we
sell Aeons we sell pandas we're raking
in money from hardware so we're just
gonna open-source the HD maps and give
them away for free because information
should be free what's the bet and Falcon
Heavy I think it'll work I think it'll
work I'm excited for that launch um I'm
excited to see us take over the world -
cool thanks for joining labour scobie's
I'm gonna try to do the Logan Paul thing
we're like now I just need it to like
turn off automatically but I can't do
that
I'm a terrible vlog